hokkaido-rusutsu.com 2018-08-21

# Privacy policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Rusutsu Resort (hereinafter referred to as“we”) acknowledges that protecting its customer's privacy and private information (hereinafter referred to as“private information”) is part of its social responsibility and has stipulated a private information protection policy to properly handle and protect private information.

**Definition of private information**  
Private information handled by we refer to customer names, addresses, telephone numbers, e-mail addresses, dates of birth and other identifiable information provided when customers use our accommodation and other facilities or services.

**Notifying the purpose of use and prohibiting unintended uses**  
We notify its customers of the purpose of using their private information before obtaining such information from them and uses it for the intended purpose only.

**Proper management**  
We stipulate regulations regarding the handling of private information to ensure its proper management.

**Employee education**  
We regularly provide its employees with educational sessions to ensure the proper handling of personal information.

**Contractor management**  
We properly manage our contractors when outsourcing the handling of personal information.

**Observation of laws and regulations**  
Regarding the handling of personal information, we abide by laws, guidelines, etc. concerning the protection of personal information.

**Miscellaneous**  
This company may revise its personal information policy to improve the handling of personal information.

### **How do we share your personal information with third parties?**

  * _BookingSuite:_ Your personal data may be shared with BookingSuite B.V. located at Herengracht 597, 1017 CE Amsterdam, the Netherlands, the company which operates this website and the website suite.booking.com. 
  * BookingSuite will provide your information which may include personal data to Booking.com for the purposes described above.
